<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>/dev/null</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on /dev/null</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 09:24:11 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>PPLs that scale</title>
      <link>/post/ppl_design/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 09:24:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/ppl_design/</guid>
      <description>Let me state two things:
 I am a Bayesian at heart. I have been using Bayesian methods professionally for 5 years now; I do not claim to be an expert in the field, and there are a lot of people smarter than me who have been thinking about these problems for a lot longer than I have.  A traditional program may look like this:
Where there&#39;s improvement  Make use of multi-core computations / GPU computation Bayesian knowledge updating Mini-batch updates  P(\theta|\mathcal{D}_1) = \frac{\P(\mathcal{D}_1|\theta) P(\theta)}{P(\mathcal{D}_1} \propto P(\mathcal{D}_1|\theta) Much of the practical &amp;amp; theoretical debate has been focusing on the choice of priors, which for me is a non-debate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iterate fast, document faster</title>
      <link>/post/iterate-fast-document-faster/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 07:43:28 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/iterate-fast-document-faster/</guid>
      <description>Every respectable startup employee will tell you: iteration speed is key to success. It is actually the best predictor of a company&#39;s success. Why iterate quickly, though? Because before finding your product-market fit you are in a learning phase, and you better learn fast before the market swallows you.
At Sounds we pride ourselves in always having a version of the application in review at the App Store, which mean a release cycle of the order of 4 days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 minutes recommendation (and tf-idf)</title>
      <link>/post/5-minutes-recommendation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 22:11:10 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/5-minutes-recommendation/</guid>
      <description>I hate complex solutions. I really do. I don&#39;t know if this comes form my background in physics where simplicity is hailed as the greatest virtue, my background in philosophy of science, or my job as chief scientist in a small startup. I live by the mantra
 A simple model in production tomorrow is better than a deep learning solution in 6 months.
 This might not apply if you work for a company that has the luxury to hire 100 data scientist (lucky you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I learned to stop worrying and love A/B tests</title>
      <link>/post/decision-theory-abtests/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 22:11:10 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/decision-theory-abtests/</guid>
      <description>A/B testing and existential angst So, you run A/B tests. Let me guess.
You often found yourself curled into a ball in anticipation of a product meeting, dreading the &amp;ldquo;are you sure about this?&amp;rdquo; question. Because no, you&#39;re not sure. Unless, of course, the improvement is above 10%, in which case you wouldn&#39;t have needed an A/B test anyway.
You often cannot sleep at night, thinking &amp;ldquo;what if my A/B tests are all wrong?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>